Become a hitman.
London Calling is a action, crime, comedy film directed by Allan Ungar.
After fleeing the UK from a job gone wrong, a down on his luck hitman is forced to
babysit the son of his new crime boss and show him how to become a man.
Tommy Ward, played by Josh Duhamel.
Freddy Darby, played by Aidan Gillen.
Julian Darby, played by Jeremy Ray Taylor.
Benson, played by Rick Hoffman.
Harry, played by Arnold Vosloo.
Barnabus, played by Daniel Lasker.
London Calling is a 2025 American action comedy film directed by Allan Ungar
and written by Omer Levin Menekse, Quinn Wolfe and Ungar.
It stars Josh Duhamel, Jeremy Ray Taylor, Rick Hoffman, and Aidan Gillen.
The film explores themes of south africa, teenage boy,
contract killer, action comedy, comedy thriller.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.